Experiences

Masterly Notion. Back-end developer. 2021-01 2022-02

Developed websites using Codelgniter, JQuery, MySQL, JavaScript, PHP and HTML.

2020-08 Smart Technology Solutions. Back-end developer. 2021-05

Developed websites using Laravel, Codelgniter, JQuery, MySQL, JavaScript, PHP, HTML, and CSS.

2018-06 2018-08

Korasond. Computer Science Internship.

Analyzed and tested an app and some websites.

Designed the UI of an android app using Android Studio.

Designed the UI of a website using WordPress.

Education

King Abdulaziz University, Executive Master in Cyber Security. 2021-09 present

King Abdulaziz University, Bachelor of Computer Science. 2015 2019 GPA: Very Good (B+).

Specialized track: Intelligent Systems.

⟨/> Projects

Diving Buddy.

An android app that automates diving plan & integrate diving log with buddies albums. By using Xamarin. Android and Firebase.

Image Processing.

An android app that adds some effects to photos by implementing Gaussian Sharpness, Gaussian Blur, and Median Blur algorithms. Using Android Studio and OpenCV library.

Photo Gallery System.

Web Albums to save user's albums online & the site administrator can control user accounts. Using PHP, HTML, JQuery, CSS, Bootstrap, and MySQL.

Certificates

Center for Outdoor Ethics, Leave No Trace. 2021-04

Doroob, Communication In The Workplace. 2021-07

Doroob, Explore Yourself. 2021-01

Udemy, How to Stop Procrastinating. 2020-11

Udemy, Build a PHP MVC Framework from Scratch. 2020-10

Udemy, HTML and CSS course. 2020-05

Knowledge & Human Development Authority, CyberSecurity Bootcamp. 2019-10

TechCampus, Cyber CTF Challenges Course. 2019-10

2019-10 TechCampus, CEH V10 Training Course.

TechCampus, Cyber Linux PenTest Course. 2019-10

TechCampus, CompTIA Security+ Training course. 2019-09

King Abdulaziz University, Intelligent System Track. 2018

KAU, Participation in the 6th FCIT EOSS. 2018-12

PADI, Advanced Open Water Diver. 2018-07

KAU, Participation in the 5th FCIT EOSS. 2018-04

KAU, Participation in the 4th FCIT End of Semester Symposium. 2017-12

Dubai Aquarium & Underwater Zoo, Shark Dive. 2015-03

Summary

Computer Science graduate. Who has two years experience in customer service. Has a high ability to adapt to work pressures, analyze difficulties, and love to take on new challenges.



Teamwork

Communication

Friendly customer service

Customer service

Fast-Learning



Analysis & Problem Solving





Hobbies

- Serving drinks.
- Diving.
- Paragliding.
- Hiking.



Recommendations

Mr. Alhasan Shahwan, Head of Digital Cloud Solutions, Smart Technology Solutions.



Software

- PHP, Laravel & CodeIgniter.
- HTML, CSS & Bootstrap.
- Java, JavaScript & jQuery.
- Nestis.
- C# & Xamarin.
- Android Studio.
- Python.
- SQL, MySQL.
- Firebase, Mongo DB.
- cPanel.
- Burp Suite.
- Wireshark.
- Cisco Packet Tracer.
- Linux (MacOS, Kali & Bee-Box).